<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
<lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 21:50:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
<ttl>1</ttl>
<generator>kagami v0.6.5 — static microblog processor</generator>
<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
<atom:link href="https://microsounds.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
<link>https://microsounds.github.io</link>
<title>sentimental µsounds</title>
<description>unix and post-ironic anemoia, µsounds' starlit diary</description>
<item>
<title>Selected documentation and usage notes for my dotfiles</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[Revision No. 847, commit 52de66f. “Added some utility scripts” View changelog since the last revision as [ diff HEAD~1...HEAD][2] The verbosity factor of this document compared to comment lines of code in this repo is about 5:1. If this document is 27.9KiB in size, and the approximate size of all comment lines of code is 62.0KiB then this document currently covers about 9.01% of all implemented features and behavior in this repository. This is just an [automated guess][1] though. This [..]]]>
<![CDATA[<br/>Read more at <a href="https://microsounds.github.io/notes/dotfiles.htm">https://microsounds.github.io/notes/dotfiles.htm</a>]]>
</description>
<link>https://microsounds.github.io/notes/dotfiles.htm</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://microsounds.github.io/notes/dotfiles.htm</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 21:50:00 -0700</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>My Collection of Assorted Figurines</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[ Last updated Here’s my small IRL collection of figurines and other assorted cute things. Most are “prize figures” of the variety you could win from a Japanese [“skill” claw machine][claw]. Unfortunately, I live an ocean away from a UFO catcher full of figurines of my [one and only muse][muse], so I can only buy them. I don’t feel like actually making an account on [myfigurecollection.net][mfc] to tell people about them though. This page will do for now, links take [..]]]>
<![CDATA[<br/>Read more at <a href="https://microsounds.github.io/notes/figures.htm">https://microsounds.github.io/notes/figures.htm</a>]]>
</description>
<link>https://microsounds.github.io/notes/figures.htm</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://microsounds.github.io/notes/figures.htm</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>List of low profile GPUs for small form factor PCs (SFFs)</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[ Last updated . NOTICE I cannot recommend going the SFF route at this time, or even the discrete GPU route in general, every worthwhile card on this list has skyrocketed in price on the used market. Most GPU marketing materials will use the term LP or “low profile” to refer to graphics cards that are half the height of a normal GPU, not full-height short-length GPUs meant for Mini-ITX cases. These are ideal for use in space-saving PCs, small [..]]]>
<![CDATA[<br/>Read more at <a href="https://microsounds.github.io/notes/low-profile-gpus-for-sff-pcs.htm">https://microsounds.github.io/notes/low-profile-gpus-for-sff-pcs.htm</a>]]>
</description>
<link>https://microsounds.github.io/notes/low-profile-gpus-for-sff-pcs.htm</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://microsounds.github.io/notes/low-profile-gpus-for-sff-pcs.htm</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>On Copyleft and why I use GPLv3</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[ This is a short outline on guaranteeing creative freedom to users of your works through copyleft. Licensing of creative works is an extremely tiresome topic so I keep all my opinions on intellectual property law contained to this page. You can use the term “software” in place of “creative works” and it should have the same gist. I release my creative works under a strong [copyleft license][copyleft] with an attribution and sharealike requirement for several reasons— I want future [..]]]>
<![CDATA[<br/>Read more at <a href="https://microsounds.github.io/notes/why-copyleft.htm">https://microsounds.github.io/notes/why-copyleft.htm</a>]]>
</description>
<link>https://microsounds.github.io/notes/why-copyleft.htm</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://microsounds.github.io/notes/why-copyleft.htm</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
